

Mateusz Kluczek

Mathematician

♀ Cork, Ireland

Profile

I am currently a PhD student in Applied Math. I take a part in research project Nonlinear Wave-Current Interaction in the Nearshore. I am self-motivated committed and determined in achieving my goals. I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problem solving. I also have a firm sense of responsibility and capacity to work under pressure.

Work experience

PhD Student – University College Cork – Cork, Ireland

October 2015 - Current

PhD program in Applied Math on nonlinear geophysical water waves. Strong background in teaching and learning. Providing lectures and tutorials.

Auditor – ING Bank Śląski – Warsaw, Poland March 2015 – September 2015

Internal auditor analysing key risk area. Designed new systems of controls. Trained in Compliance and operational Risk. Preparing reports of audits and closing recommendations.

Details

53 Cardinal Court Cork,Ireland

+353834874877 kluczek.m@gmail.com

Date/Place of birth 19/06/1991 Siedlce, Poland



LATEX
MATLAB
Wolfram Mathematica
MS Office
JAVA



Languages

Polish – native English – fluent German – basic

Work experience

Researcher – Siedlce University of Natural Sciences and Humanities – Siedlce, Poland

October 2014 – July 2015

Part of research team in "Accurate And Approximate Algorithms For Large-Scale Stochastic Simulation". Verifying new codes and algorithms describing particle movement in interplanetary space. Background in numerical analysis and computer programming.

Internship – BGŻ BNP Paribas – Siedlce, Poland June 2012 – August 2012

Internal and external flow of information and documents. Training in economics and credit risk analysis.

Publications

M. Kluczek, Equatorial water waves with underlying currents in the f-plane approximation. Applicable Analysis (2017), doi:10.1080/00036811.2017.1343466.

A.R. Sanjurjo, M. Kluczek, Mean flow properties for equatorially trapped internal water wave-current interactions. Applicable Analysis (2016), doi:10.1080/00036811.2016.1221943.

M. Kluczek, Exact and explicit internal Equatorially-trapped water waves with underlying currents. Journal of Mathematical Fluid Mechanics, 19 (2017), 305314.

A. Wawrzyńczak, R. Modzelewska, M. Kluczek, Numerical methods for solution of the stochastic differential equations equivalent to the non-stationary Parker's transport equation. Journal of Physics Conference Series 633, doi:10.1088/1742-6596/633/1/012058

Education

University College Cork – Cork, Ireland

2015 – Current

PhD program in nonlinear wave-current interactions in the nearshore.

Siedlce University of Natural Sciences and Humanities – Siedlce, Poland

2010 - 2015

Postgraduate degree of Financial Mathematics. Undergraduate degree of Financial and Actuarial Mathematics.

Siedlce University of Natural Sciences and Humanities – Siedlce, Poland

2012 - 2013

Training to national exam for Stock Exchange Trader.